Yes, welcome back to my channel. In July,
I gave an exam of some series.
Now, I became a mutual fund
distributor. So, I have been employed
with ICC Prudential. So, I am
sharing my welcome kit with all of you guys.
So, I received a welcome kit
from ICC Prudential. It was
received directly at my home.
Inside, we have received this letter first.
ICC Prudential has celebrated your
progress as a priority. Tell us what we have in it.
Inside the kit, I have
protossed
samples from ICC application forms and at the
end it is written that we welcome you on board
today as a partner of ICC Prudential.
On the next page, this is the list of their contact
address management.
Ahmedabad, Bangalore and Vadodara,
Goregaon, Hyderabad, Indore, Kolhapur,
Kolkata. So, there are total 36 branches of
ICC Prudential.
Next, I received a letter from the campus
in which it was told that ICC Mutual
I have been enrolled
in the panel with the fund and I am getting a welcome kit.
Next, this is a father letter
that we have to follow the guidelines etc.
and mutual fund investment today is a subject to
market rest read the scheme related
documents carefully so after this is Inter
World of Growth Welcome to ICC
Prudential
Promise of Growth by that and next pay
this as know your scheme and your hand right know
this n so every growth this is all
our schemes in this it is
like a big brochure in which many
schemes like I to AC balance advance
Bluetooth have been
explained in big it
how can we access it how to do what
and next take my to do list
this is what an I proof touch how
our application will be accessed and give me my to do
list
and next no water correctly film form
should look like it has some sample forms in it as to
how we have to file these forms
and next I have this booklet
which has information memorandum and general
Application form for multiple schemes and
investment options, there is a lot of information in it
which is our scheme
related information which we call all
and next last there is a
partner's handbook in which the
details of ICC Prudential are written, in this
we have been told a lot of things like
how to file the general application form,
settlement is done
in the big of ICC Prudential and a little bit
so thoughts on today thank you but watching me
video State Union with me channel more
updates thank you